#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ mcsheasrepairs (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Maintenance & Repair Property Management Painting

# Michael McShea

Painter / Drywall Finisher

Los Angeles Metropolitan Area

### Summary

Mike of all trades. 20 years of work experience. I've gone through Job Corps and Deepsea Dive Trade School. Worked on dozens of Apartments and Single Family Homes for New Construction, Repairs and Flips. Trained on Fork and Scissor Lifts. Constructed, Set up and Demolished stores(Target, Lowe's, Auto Zone, Verizon, Home Depot, AMC Theater). Was able to Train new hires, Lead Labor Crews and Manage Sales Floors.

### Experience

PeopleReady Skilled Laborer 2017 - Present (6 years)

Canoga Park

Mixture of cleaning construction sites, heavy lifting materials. Unloading trucks. Driving Forklifts. Operation of scissor lift. Remodeling stores like Target, CVS, Home Depot Lowe's.

So cal climate control Handy Man January 2020 - Present (3 years 4 months)

Repairs drywall once unit is removed

Jacks Rebuilds Senior Maintenance Technician 2013 - Present (10 years) Canoga Park

Light plumbing, electrical, carpentry, landscaping and painting. Flipping homes for rental.

## Education

Big Bend Community College

GED, General Studies · (August 2000 - September 2000)